See how far we've come together
And we are stronger than before
And these are memories we'll cherish more and more
We'll walk as one with dawn
May your courage never fail you
Your future's yours alone to write
And may our shared ideas cut through the haze of time
Amidst where stars arise
I'll carry this light moving strong I'll tell
it our hardship is to learn
We're made for this moment We're chosen and we know it
Today is the day we're never to fly ever so high
May your courage never fail you
Your future's yours alone to write
And may our shared ideas come through the haze of time
A mist where stars arise
We're shining so bright as the sun
We're rising so high above the storm
In search of good and all in
We're focusing devoted
Let's rise
Night or daylight You know the light of mine
I'll carry this light moving strong
I'll tear it when hardship is too far
We're waiting for this moment
We're chosen and we know it Today is now or never
We're shining so bright as the sun
We're rising so high above the stars
In search of truth and knowledge
We're focused and devoted Let's rise
Night or daylight
Keep going right or left
© transcript Emily Beynon